Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Conventions
  - RavenCon
    - RavenCon 2011, 29 Apr 2016 to 01 May 2016
      - Od-Ditties: A Filk Album by Danny Birt, Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011, Notes: Somnifacient Records Origin: Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011 by Chris Mezzolesta of VoiceGuy 1 Communications Convention: RavenCon 2011; Commercial CD 1 copy; Birt, Danny; Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011 by Chris Me
        Birt, Danny; Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011 by Chris Mezzolesta of VoiceGuy 1 Communications; Birt, Danny; Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011 by Chris Mezzolesta of VoiceGuy 1 Communications; Recorded Live at RavenCon 2011 by Chris Mezzolesta of VoiceGuy 1 Communications; Convention--RavenCon 2011; Commercial CD
  - Relaxicon
    - Harmuni, the Briitsh Filk Relaxicon, 14 Aug 2001 to 26 Aug 2001
      York University, Britain?
      - Live at Harmuni, 2001; Notes: Origin: Convention: Harmuni, the Briitsh Filk Relaxicon; Commercial CD 1 copy; Sampson, Mich (Box Box #03 (I))
        Sampson, Mich; Sampson, Mich; Convention--Harmuni, the Briitsh Filk Relaxicon; Commercial CD
  - Rivercon
    - Rivercon II, 1976
      - Rivercon 1976 90 min, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon II: 1976; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon II: 1976; Tape
    - Rivercon IV, 1978
      - Rivercon 1978, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon IV: 1978; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon IV: 1978; Tape
    - Rivercon V, 1980
      - Rivercon 1980, Notes: label only on case (tape says: "R 80") Origin: Convention: Rivercon V: 1980; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon V: 1980; Tape
    - Rivercon VI, 1981
      - Rivercon VI 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon VI; Tape
      - Rivercon VI 11, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VI 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VI 5-6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VI 7-8, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VI 9-10, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Rivercon VII, 1982
      - Rivercon 7 1, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon VII; Tape
      - Rivercon VII #2, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VII #3, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VII #4, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VII #5, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon VII #6, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Bold Marauder Rivercon 1982, Notes: label only on case; tape says: "Bold Marauder Tape" Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII: 1982; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon VII: 1982; Tape
      - Rivercon 1982, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII: 1982; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon 1982 (1) Fri Night From Babcock, Notes: label only on case (tape says: "Rivercon '82 Duplicate") Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII: 1982; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon 1982 (2) Fri Night From Babcock, Notes: label only on case (tape says: "Rivercon '82 Duplicate"); also contains mailing label (photographed) Origin: Convention: Rivercon VII: 1982; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Rivercon VIII, 1983
      - Rivercon 1983 1, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VIII: 1983; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon VIII: 1983; Tape
      - Rivercon 1983 2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon VIII: 1983; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Rivercon IX, 1984
      - Rivercon IX 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon IX; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon IX; Tape
      - Rivercon IX 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon IX; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon IX 5-6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon IX; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon IX 7-8, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon IX; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Rivercon X, 1985
      - Rivercon X 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon X; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon X; Tape
      - Rivercon X 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon X; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon X 5-6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon X; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon X 7-8, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon X; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Rivercon XI, 1986
      - Rivercon XI 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon XI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon XI; Tape
      - Rivercon XI 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon XI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon XI 5-6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon XI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rivercon 1986, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Rivercon XI: 1986; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon XI: 1986; Tape
    - Rivercon XII, 31 Jul 1987 to 02 Aug 1987
      - Rivercon 1987, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Rivercon XII: 1987; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Rivercon XII: 1987; Tape
  - Shore Leave
    - Shore Leave 8, 18 Jul 1985 to 20 Jul 1985
  - SilverCon
    - SilverCon, 01 Apr 1993 to 03 Apr 1993
      Las Vegas, NV
      - Woad Warrior, 1993; Notes: Origin: Dandelion Digital "Building Bridges Through Music" 3078 Sulphur Spring Court, San Jose, California, 95148 Convention: SilverCon; Commercial CD 1 copy; SilverCon 2, Las Vegas, NV 1-3 April, 1993; Dandelion Digital "Building Bridges Through Music" 3078 Sulphur Spring Court, San Jose, California, 95148 (Box Box #03 (I))
        SilverCon 2, Las Vegas, NV 1-3 April, 1993; Dandelion Digital "Building Bridges Through Music" 3078 Sulphur Spring Court, San Jose, California, 95148; Various; Dandelion Digital "Building Bridges Through Music" 3078 Sulphur Spring Court, San Jose, California, 95148; Convention--SilverCon; Commercial CD
  - Smofcon
    - Smofcon 25, 07 Dec 2007 to 09 Dec 2007
      - The Smofcon 25 Complaints Choir Songbook, 2007; Notes: Yellow cover with large singing head, staple bound Origin: Convention: Smofcon 25: 2007; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Various; Convention--Smofcon 25: 2007; Songbook
      - The Smofcon 25 Complaints Choir Songbook, 2007; Notes: Yellow cover with large singing head, staple bound Origin: Convention: Smofcon 25: 2007; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        various; Convention--Smofcon 25: 2007; Songbook
  - Spacecon
    - Spacecon 3, 17 Jul 1981 to 19 Jul 1981
      Wapakoneta, Ohio
      - Juanita Coulson Spacecon 3 7/18/81 / Joe Haldeman, 18 July 1981; Notes: Origin: Convention: Spacecon 3; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
        Coulson, Juanita; Convention--Spacecon 3; Tape - Home recorded cassette
  - Westercon
    - Episode XXXX, 02 Jul 1987 to 05 Jul 1987
      Oakland, CA
      - Manifilk Destiny, Notes: WS013 Origin: Convention: Episode XXXX: 1987; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Episode XXXX: 1987; Professional Cassette
      - Manifilk Destiny 161, Notes: WS013: photocopy of the full official liner notes Origin: Convention: Episode XXXX: 1987; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Episode XXXX: 1987; Tape
    - Conozoic, 01 Jul 1994 to 04 Jul 1994
      - Westercon 1994 - #1 (1-4) #4 (5-8), Notes: Origin: Convention: Conozoic: 1994; Hi8 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--Conozoic: 1994; Hi8
      - Westercon 1994 - #2 (1-4) #5 (5-8), Notes: Origin: Convention: Conozoic: 1994; Hi8 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - Westercon '94 #3 (1-4) #6 (5-8), 1994; Notes: Origin: Convention: Conozoic: 1994; Hi8 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
  - Whatcon
    - Whatcon II, 1980
      - Whatcon II 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Whatcon II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Whatcon II; Tape
      - Whatcon II 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Whatcon II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Whatcon II 5-6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Whatcon II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
  - Windycon
    - Windycon VII, 1980
      - Windycon VII 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon VII; Tape
      - Windycon VII 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Windycon VII 5-6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon VII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - #17 Windy Con '80 // Fish (#1), Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon VII: 1980; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon VII: 1980; Tape
      - #2 WindyCon 80 / Fish 18, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon VII: 1980; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - #3 WindyCon 80 / Fish 19, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon VII: 1980; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Windycon VIII, 1981
      - Windycon VIII 5-6, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Windycon VIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon VIII; Tape
      - Windycon VIII 9-10, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Windycon VIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Side 1 WindyCon 1981, Notes: label only on case (and paper slip in case, that reads: "(2) Windycon Side 1 Only (incomplete)" Origin: Convention: Windycon VIII: 1981; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon VIII: 1981; Tape
      - Windycon 1981, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon VIII: 1981; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Windycon XI, 1984
      - Windycon XI 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon XI; Tape
      - Windycon XI 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - #51 Windy-Con = 12/84, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XI: 1984; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon XI: 1984; Tape
    - Windycon XII, 1985
      - Windycon XII 1-2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon XII; Tape
      - Windycon XII 3-4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Windycon XII 5-6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Idicon #3 - Tape 2 / Windycon 85 103, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XII: 1985; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon XII: 1985; Tape
    - Windycon XIII, 1986
      - Windycon VIII 1-2, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Windycon XIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon XIII; Tape
      - Windycon VIII 3-4, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Windycon XIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Windycon XIII (1), Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Windycon XIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Windycon XIII 11-12, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Windycon XIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Windycon XIII (3), Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Windycon XIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Windycon XIII 7-8, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Windycon XIII; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Windycon VI, 07 Oct 1977 to 09 Oct 1977
      Arlington Heights, IL
      - Windycon VI Friday, Notes: label on tape and case (slightly more detail on tape) Origin: Convention: Windycon VI; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon VI; Tape
    - Windycon XVII, 09 Nov 1990 to 11 Nov 1990
      - Windycon - 1990 179, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Windycon XVII: 1990; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Windycon XVII: 1990; Tape
    - Windycon 33, 10 Nov 2006 to 12 Nov 2006
      Rosemont, IL
      - Eloise Mason November 2006 Concert, 1 November 2006; Notes: Origin: Convention: Windycon 33: 2006; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
        Convention--Windycon 33: 2006; Burnt CD
    - Windycon 43, 11 Nov 2016 to 13 Nov 2016
      Lombard, IL
      - Live at Windycon, 2017; Notes: Origin: Convention: Windycon 43: 2016; Commercial CD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
        Ookla the Mok; Convention--Windycon 43: 2016; Commercial CD
  - Worldcon
    - WorldCon 37, Seacon '79, 23 Aug 1979 to 26 Aug 1979
      Brighton, UK
      - Seacon '79 - Alein Dream [tiny handwritten label], Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 37, Seacon '79; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
        Convention--WorldCon 37, Seacon '79; Tape
    - WorldCon 40, Chicon IV, 02 Sep 1982 to 06 Sep 1982
      - Chicon IV -(2), Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape
      - Chicon IV (1), Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Chicon IV (3), Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Chicon IV (4), Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Chicon IV JK. T2 S1, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Chicon IV JK T5S1, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Chicon IV JK T6S1, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Chicon IV T4 S1, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - JK Chicon IV T3 S1, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - The Best of Chi-Con IV, Notes: OCP-12: 3 different color papers used for printing the liner notes Origin: Convention: WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--WorldCon 40, Chicon IV; Professional Cassette
    - WorldCon 41, ConStellation, 01 Sep 1983 to 05 Sep 1983
      - Constellation 1, Notes: label on tape and case (tape additionally says: A: "Thurs. Night"; B: "Sat + Sun Nights") Origin: Convention: WorldCon 41, ConStellation; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--WorldCon 41, ConStellation; Tape
      - Constellation 2, Notes: label on tape and case (tape additionally says: "Sun") Origin: Convention: WorldCon 41, ConStellation; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - The Best of ConStellation, Notes: OCP-23 Origin: Convention: WorldCon 41, ConStellation; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--WorldCon 41, ConStellation; Professional Cassette
      - The Best of ConStellation [OCP-23], Notes: OCP-23 is printed on the tape; cases are identical Origin: Convention: WorldCon 41, ConStellation; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - #37 World-Con - '83, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 41, ConStellation: 1983; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--WorldCon 41, ConStellation: 1983; Tape
      - #38 World-Con - '83, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 41, ConStellation: 1983; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Worldcon 42, LACon II, 30 Aug 1984 to 03 Sep 1984
      - A Little Rat Music, 1984; Notes: OCP-41 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 42, LACon II: 1984; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
        Convention--Worldcon 42, LACon II: 1984; Professional Cassette
      - Rat Mastersongs, 1984; Notes: OCP-40 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 42, LACon II: 1984; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
    - Worldcon 43, Aussiecon II, 22 Aug 1985 to 26 Aug 1985
      - The Wail From Down Under, Notes: WS006: tape labels are falling off Origin: Convention: Worldcon 43, Aussiecon II: 1985; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Worldcon 43, Aussiecon II: 1985; Professional Cassette
    - WorldCon 44, ConFederation, 28 Aug 1986 to 01 Sep 1986
      - Confederation - Yankee Doodles & / Rebel Yells 122, Notes: label on tape and case (slightly different) Origin: Convention: WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Tape
      - Confederation 1986 Pro-Filk, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Rebel Yells, Notes: OCP-82 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_rebel_yells Convention: WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Professional Cassette 4 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Professional Cassette
      - WorldCon'86-ATL-Confederation-Mon, Dead Dog Filk, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - World Con 1986 Saturday, Notes: label on tape and case (tape says: "Confederation Saturday") Origin: Convention: WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Yankee Doodles, Notes: OCP-83 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_yankee_doodles Convention: WorldCon 44, ConFederation: 1986; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
    - WorldCon 46, Nolacon II, 01 Sep 1988 to 05 Sep 1988
      - Harlequinade, Notes: WS018 Origin: Convention: WorldCon 46, Nolacon II; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--WorldCon 46, Nolacon II; Professional Cassette
      - Harlequinade 149, Notes: WS018: partial photocopy of official liner notes Origin: Convention: WorldCon 46, Nolacon II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--WorldCon 46, Nolacon II; Tape
      - Harlequinery, Notes: WS019 Origin: Convention: WorldCon 46, Nolacon II; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Harlequinery 148, Notes: WS019: partial photocopy of official liner notes Origin: Convention: WorldCon 46, Nolacon II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
    - Worldcon 47, Noreascon 3, 31 Aug 1989 to 04 Sep 1989
      - Caterwauls Noreascon 3, Notes: WS025 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 47, Noreascon 3; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Worldcon 47, Noreascon 3; Professional Cassette
      - Caterwauls Noreascon 3 190, Notes: WS025: photocopy of the full official liner notes Origin: Convention: Worldcon 47, Noreascon 3; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Worldcon 47, Noreascon 3; Tape
      - Courtly Airs 189, Notes: WS024: photocopy of the full official liner notes Origin: Convention: Worldcon 47, Noreascon 3; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Courtly Airs Noreascon 3, Notes: WS024 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 47, Noreascon 3; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
    - Worldcon 49, Chicon V, 29 Aug 1991 to 02 Sep 1991
      - Mists of Memory Chicon V, Notes: WS038 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 49, Chicon V; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Worldcon 49, Chicon V; Professional Cassette
    - Worldcon 50, Magicon, 03 Sep 1992 to 07 Sep 1992
      Orlando, FL
      - Magico Eurofilk 6-9, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape
      - Magicon LLF #2, Notes: Return to Eli - In a case that says Musicon '93 Dumps for Nick #1 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
        Convention--Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape - Home recorded cassette
      - Magicon Mon Dead dog 1-3, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Magicon Sun Con 1-4, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Magicon Thurs 3-6, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Magicon Thurs 7-8 / Eurofilk 1, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Magicon Wed 9-10 / Thurs 1-2, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - Magicon Wednesday 1-4 LLF 3A, Notes: Return to Eli - In a case that says ConAdian Tape 1 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      - Worldcon: Fish/Sutton - Magicon, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - LLF Magicon #1, Notes: Return to Eli Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon: 1992; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
        Convention--Worldcon 50, Magicon: 1992; Tape - Home recorded cassette
      - Worldcon 92 Aquarium, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon: 1992; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Worldcon 50, Magicon: 1992; Tape
      - Worldcon Aquarium - 1992, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 50, Magicon: 1992; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
    - Worldcon 52, ConAdian, 01 Sep 1993 to 05 Sep 1993
      Winnipeg, MB
      - ConAdian-Tape 6-A, Notes: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape
      - ConAdian - 2, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - ConAdian - 2 (black tape, red ink), Notes: label only on tape (case says: "FilkoNtario 3: tapes 9-12") Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - ConAdian - 3, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - ConAdian - 3 (clear tape, blue ink), Notes: label only on tape (case says: "Phoenix + Murray Porath "We won't share..."") Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - ConAdian - 4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - ConAdian - 5, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - ConAdian - 6, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - ConAdian - Tape 1, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Worldcon 52, ConAdian; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))